* *
**
Who needs a bathroom
when I can shave
谁需要卫生间
当我可以刮胡子的时候
and drive to work
at the same time
并开车去上班
同时
- Ahh! Uhh! Ahh!
- 啊！呃！啊！
Watch where you're going,
you miniscule maniac!
看你要去哪里
你这个小疯子！
- Get bent, Krabs!
- 弯曲吧，蟹蟹们！
Ehh.
呃。
- Ohh! Ohh! Ohh!
- 哦！哦！哦！
Ohh! Ah! You maniac!
哦！啊!你这个疯子！
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
哦，哦，哦，哦！
Ohh!
哦！
- Outta my way, you fool!
- 别挡我的路，你这个傻瓜！
Hm?
嗯？
Ehh! Ow!
呃！噢！
Ohh, shrimp!
哦，虾！
- Ohh, you--I--this--
- 哦，你--我--这个--
No!
不！
Traffic School!
交通学校！
- Ehh, you cause a little
300 boat pile-up,
- 呃，你造成了一点
300艘船连环相撞，
and they send you
to boating school.
他们送你
去划船学校。
Eh, well, better make the most
of it and grab the best desk.
呃，好吧，最好充分利用
并抓住最好的桌子。
Ahh.
啊。
Ohh!
哦！
Easy with that heinie, Eugene.
轻松点，尤金。
This is my desk!
这是我的办公桌！
You can have it.
你可以拥有它。
I'll just take this one.
我就拿这个吧。
- Ohh, you want me to take this
garbage desk
- 哦，你想让我接受这个
垃圾台
so you can grab that prime seat
and get all
这样你就可以抢到最好的座位
并得到所有
the teacher's attention?
老师的关注？
Well, forget it.
That one's mine.
好吧，算了。
那是我的。
Oh!
哦！
Dibs! Ahh!
迪布斯！啊！
Aha!
- This one's mine!
啊哈！
- 这个是我的！
Yikes!
- Ahh! Ahh!
哎呀！
- 啊！啊！
- And this one's mine.
- Ahh! Ahh!
- 这个是我的。
- 啊！啊！
- This one's mine!
- No, it's mine!
- 这个是我的！
- 不，这是我的！
- Mine! Mine!
- 矿！矿！
- Oh! My classroom! Stop!
- 哦！我的教室！停止！
- Ooh, sorry, cutie.
- Suck up.
- 哦，对不起，小可爱。
- 吸吮。
- Ohh, it's on.
- Ohh, bring it!
- 哦，已经开始了。
- 哦，拿来吧！
- Ohh, I said knock it off.
- 哦，我说别说了。
Now don't make me get rough.
现在别让我变得粗暴。
Respect.
尊重。
- Now just settle down and watch
this movie on driving safety.
- 现在坐下来观看
这部关于驾驶安全的电影。
- Oh, yes. The freedom
of the open road.
- 哦是的。自由
的开放道路。
The feeling of the wind
in your hair
风的感觉
在你的头发里
and the sun on your shoulders.
和你肩上的阳光。
Yes, there's nothing
like driving.
是的，什么都没有
就像开车一样。
But when you don't
follow the rules,
但当你不这样做时
遵守规则，
Driving can become deadly.
驾驶可能会致命。
From cruising down the highway
从高速公路上行驶
to parallel parking.
平行停车。
- Oh, no, sorry!
- 哦，不，抱歉！
Sorry! Oh, sorry.
- You don't want to be
对不起！哦，抱歉。
- 你不想成为
a SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
- So remember to follow
these simple rules.
- 所以记得关注
这些简单的规则。
Number one, always remember
to check your mirrors.
第一，永远记住
检查你的镜子。
- Uh-oh!
- 呃哦！
- Yeah!
- 是的！
- Oh! Ahh!
- 哦！啊！
- Hey, cool camera.
Can I see?
- 嘿，很酷的相机。
我可以看吗？
Ahh! Ooh! Ohh.
啊！哦！哦。
- Ehh, ahh.
- 呃，啊。
Whoa. Sorry I'm late.
哇哦。抱歉我来晚了。
- SpongeBob, I told you before,
- 海绵宝宝，我之前告诉过你，
use the door!
使用门！
- Sorry, Mrs. Puff.
I was so excited for class,
- 对不起，帕芙女士。
上课的时候我很兴奋
I must've forgot.
我一定是忘记了。
- Just clean this place up.
- 把这个地方打扫干净就可以了。
I need to call my therapist.
我需要打电话给我的治疗师。
- Ooh, this is so great having
you in class with me, Mr. Krabs.
- 哦，这真是太棒了
你和我一起上课，蟹老板。
'Cause now, you're not only my
boss, you're also my classmate
因为现在你不仅是我的
老板，你也是我的同学
and, dare I say it,
my best friend.
而且，我敢说，
我最好的朋友。
Aww, make that two best friends.
哇，让这两个最好的朋友。
- Get off!
- 下车！
- Ohh, I think
someone is nervous
- 哦，我想
有人很紧张
about being
the new kid in class.
关于存在
班上新来的孩子。
No worry, I'll show you
all the ropes.
不用担心，我会告诉你
所有的绳索。
Did you know that every time
you do something good,
你知道吗，每次
你做了一些好事，
Mrs. Puff gives you
a star sticker?
泡芙夫人给你
星星贴纸？
I'm adult.
I don't care about stickers.
我已经成年了。
我不关心贴纸。
- Yeah, me neither.
- 是的，我也一样。
No matter how cool
and shiny they are.
不管多酷
它们很闪亮。
I'm gonna have so many stars,
我会拥有很多星星
Puff will have to get
a bigger board!
泡芙一定要得到
更大的板！
- Forget it, Eugene,
-算了，尤金，
I am going to be
the star pupil.
我将会成为
明星瞳孔。
- The prescription is
for the mega dose, right?
- 处方是
对于大剂量，对吗？
- Yes, Mrs. Puff.
- Oh, thank you Doctor.
- 是的，帕芙女士。
-哦，谢谢医生。
- Yeah, bye-bye.
- 是的，再见。
- Now, if everyone will turn
to page 20
- 现在，如果每个人都愿意
至第 20 页
in their driving manuals.
在他们的驾驶手册中。
- Oh, nothing.
- 哦，没什么。
I just thought you could
use a little snack.
我只是以为你可以
使用一点零食。
Winkety blink.
- Why, thank you.
眨眼。
- 为什么，谢谢。
You get a star.
你会得到一颗星星。
Tada!
田田！
- Oh, a grapefruit.
- 哦，一个葡萄柚。
And a star for you.
还有一颗星星送给你。
- Uh!
- 呃！
All right, boys,
enough with the fruit--
好吧，孩子们，
水果就够了——
- I want those stickers!
- 我想要那些贴纸！
- Forget it, Krabs.
They're mine! Ah!
-算了，蟹蟹。
他们是我的！啊!
- Ahh, I'm through
wasting time here.
- 啊，我结束了
在这里浪费时间。
Straight from the source.
直接从源头开始。
Uh, ah!
呃，啊！
Oh--ahh, ahh, ahh!
啊——啊啊啊啊！
- Enough!
- 足够的！
- Aw, but I want more
shiny stars!
- 哦，但我想要更多
闪亮的星星！
- No, I do!
- 不，我愿意！
You want stars?
你想要星星吗？
I'll give you stars.
我会给你星星。
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
啊啊啊啊啊！
Beautiful stars.
美丽的星星。
- Oh, I want some.
- 哦，我想要一些。
Doink! Ehh, ehh.
多因克！呃，呃。
- Give me those!
Ah, ah.
- 给我那些！
啊，啊。
- Ohh.
- 哦。
- When driving,
it's important to be aware
- 开车时，
重要的是要意识到
of everything around you.
你周围的一切。
That's why we have mirrors.
这就是为什么我们有镜子。
And that's why it's important
to constantly check our mirrors.
这就是为什么它很重要
不断检查我们的镜子。
Like this.
像这样。
- Oh, oh.
- 哦，哦。
both: Eee.
两人：哎呀。
- Hmm.
- 唔。
both: Eee.
两人：哎呀。
- Mrs. Puff,
the two new students are--
- 普芙女士，
这两名新学生是——
- Nothing. Nothing's going on.
- 没有什么。什么都没有发生。
- We swear.
- 我们发誓。
Welcome to the test track.
欢迎来到测试赛道。
Now, I want you all
to pull out slowly
现在，我想要你们所有人
慢慢地拉出来
and carefully.
并仔细地。
Understand?
- Slowly and carefully.
理解？
- 慢慢地、小心地。
Got it.
知道了。
- Now, don't--ah!
- 现在，不要——啊！
Now these are my last boats
现在这些是我最后的船
and if you wreck 'em,
none of you will pass my class.
如果你破坏了它们
你们谁都不会通过我的课。
I can't believe I'm saying this,
我不敢相信我会这么说
but be more like SpongeBob.
但更像海绵宝宝。
He hasn't acted out once.
他一次也没有表现过。
- Mrs. Puff, that's the nicest
thing you ever said about me.
- 泡芙女士，这是最好的
你曾经说过关于我的话。
- Mm! Mm, SpongeBob,
- 毫米！嗯，海绵宝宝，
the parking brake!
- Yikes! Come back, boat.
驻车制动器！
- 哎呀！回来吧，船。
Yah! Oh.
啊！哦。
- Hey! Ow, ow, ow, ooh, ow.
- 嘿！噢，噢，噢，噢，噢。
Ehh! Ehh!
呃！呃！
Ehh, ahh!
诶诶诶！
Yeah!
是的！
- Stop! Stop! I'm gonna lose
my teacher's license.
- 停止！停止！我会输
我的教师执照。
- Can't catch me, Eugene!
- 追不到我，尤金！
I'm the number one driver!
我是第一司机！
- Well, good for you,
plankton.
- 嗯，对你有好处，
浮游生物。
- Don't congratulate him
SpongeBob!
- 别祝贺他
海绵宝宝！
- Mr. Krabs, classmates
support each other
- 螃蟹先生，同学们
互相支持
and he just said
he's number one.
他只是说
他是第一。
Then let's see him do this!
那我们就来看看他这样做吧！
Ahh!
啊！
- That's easy.
- 这很容易。
- Come down from there
right now.
- 从那里下来
现在。
- Never!
- 绝不！
- I'm a god in this boat,
on my way to heaven!
- 我是这艘船上的神，
在我去天堂的路上！
- * *
- **
Top of the world!
世界之巅！
both: Uh-oh.
两人：呃哦。
That's it!
就是这样！
You both fail!
你们都失败了！
- Oh, come on!
Don't we at least
- 哦，来吧！
我们至少不
deserve some credit
for not getting hurt?
值得一些赞扬
为了不受伤？
I mean, that was
crazy dangerous.
我的意思是，那是
疯狂危险。
- Yeah, it was.
- 是的，确实如此。
- Hey, guys. I finished that--
- 嘿，伙计们。我说完了——
- Mr. Plankton, you were in
a horrible boat accident.
-浮游生物先生，你在
一次可怕的船难
It's a miracle
that you're alive.
这是一个奇迹
你还活着。
However, there were
some complications.
然而，有
一些并发症。
What complications?
有什么并发症？
- Well, there was
some confusion
- 嗯，有
一些混乱
on what body parts went where.
身体的哪些部位去了哪里。
- Hey, what's all
the screaming up there?
- 嘿，怎么了
那里的尖叫声？
Forget class, now we can
be together forever,
忘记上课，现在我们可以
永远在一起，